module.exports = [
  {
    id: 0, // optional
    question: "Which dog breeds were originally bred to fight badgers?",
    options: ["Dachshunds", "Greyhounds", "Beagles", "Boxers"], // store options in an array
    correct: "Dachshunds",
    hint: "", // optional
    fact: "", // optional
  },
  {
    id: 1, // optional
    question: "What is the largest dog breed in the world?",
    options: [
      "Scottish Deerhound",
      "Great Pyrenees",
      " Greyhound",
      "English Mastiff",
    ], // store options in an array
    correct: "English Mastiff",
    hint: "", // optional
    fact: "", // optional
  },
  {
    id: 2, // optional
    question: "How many teeth do normal adult dogs have?",
    options: ["42", "36", "44", "69"], // store options in an array
    correct: "42",
    hint: "", // optional
    fact: "", // optional
  },
  {
    id: 3, // optional
    question: "Which snake has the longest fangs?",
    options: ["Gaboon Viper", "Black Mamba", "Green anaconda", "Cottonmouths"], // store options in an array
    correct: "Gaboon Viper",
    hint: "", // optional
    fact: "", // optional
  },
  {
    id: 4, // optional
    question:
      " When a copperhead is threatened, it emits a musk that smells vaguely like:",
    options: ["Cucumbers", "Orange", "Pineapple", "Mango"], // store options in an array
    correct: "Cucumbers",
    hint: "", // optional
    fact: "", // optional
  },
  {
    id: 5, // optional
    question: "Which is the most venomous species of snake in the world?",
    options: [
      " Egyptian Cobra",
      "Mozambique Spitting Cobra.",
      "King Cobra",
      " Inland Taipan",
    ], // store options in an array
    correct: " Inland Taipan",
    hint: "", // optional
    fact: "", // optional
  },
  {
    id: 6, // optional
    question: "True or False: You can hypnotise a chicken?",
    options: ["Partially True", "False", "True", "Partially False"], // store options in an array
    correct: "True",
    hint: "", // optional
    fact: "", // optional
  },
  {
    id: 7, // optional
    question: "True or False: An Ostrich's eye is bigger than its brain?",
    options: ["Partially True", "False", "True", "Partially False"], // store options in an array
    correct: "True",
    hint: "", // optional
    fact: "", // optional
  },
  {
    id: 8, // optional
    question:
      "When animals are the same size, which is stronger, a donkey or a horse?",
    options: ["Donkey", "Horse", "Both will be same", "Mule"], // store options in an array
    correct: "Donkey",
    hint: "", // optional
    fact: "", // optional
  },
  {
    id: 9, // optional
    question:
      "True or False: Coral (in coral reefs) are plants and not animals?",
    options: ["Partially True", "False", "True", "Partially False"], // store options in an array
    correct: "Flse",
    hint: "", // optional
    fact: "", // optional
  },
  {
    id: 10, // optional
    question: "Guess The Anagram: RAPTOR",
    options: ["Parrot", "Raptor", "Trapor", "Raprot"], // store options in an array
    correct: "Parrot",
    hint: "", // optional
    fact: "", // optional
  },
  {
    id: 11, // optional
    question: "True or False: An octopus is an invertebrate?",
    options: ["Partially True", "False", "True", "Partially False"], // store options in an array
    correct: "True",
    hint: "", // optional
    fact: "", // optional
  },
  {
    id: 12, // optional
    question: "What type of creature is a Pacific Sea Wasp?",
    options: ["Jellyfish", "Octopus", "Sea urchin", "Stingray"], // store options in an array
    correct: "Jellyfish",
    hint: "", // optional
    fact: "", // optional
  },
  {
    id: 13, // optional
    question: "Guess The Anagrams: SOCCER IDOLS",
    options: ["Crocodiles", "Crockodiles", "Socerlodes", "Idolcress"], // store options in an array
    correct: "Crocodiles",
    hint: "", // optional
    fact: "", // optional
  },
  {
    id: 14, // optional
    question: "What is the name of the horse of Alexander the Great?",
    options: ["Copenhagen", "Comanche", "Bucephalus", "Chaitak"], // store options in an array
    correct: "Bucephalus",
    hint: "", // optional
    fact: "", // optional
  },
];
